Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2012, UWM Archival Collection 48; 28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - 1. Student Organization Files, 1915-2010
    - Chinmoy Meditation Centre, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Christian Science Organization
      - 1957-1994 (Box 17, Folder 87)
      - 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Christian Students, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Christians on Campus, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Chung Chin, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Church of Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Non-Mormon), 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Circle K Club, 1962-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Circle of Swords, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Cispes, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Citizens for Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Citizens Freedom Foundation-Information Service at UWM, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Citizens Utility Board, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Clams Fan Club, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Classical Civilization Club, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Club Espanol, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Club Jim Moody for Congress at UWM, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Coalition for Geopolitical Sanity, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Coalition of Concerned Students, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Coalition of Student Programmers, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Coalition United for Victory, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Coast to Coast Student Travel, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Colleagues in Action, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - College Choir, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - College Citizens of UWM, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - College Labor & Farm Party, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - College Panhellenic
      - 1965-1995 (Box 17, Folder 100)
      - Activities, 1958-1994 (Box 17, Folder 101-102)
    - College Volunteers, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles
      - 1980-1993 (Box 17, Folder 104)
      - 1981-1983, undated (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Comedy Related Artistic Productions, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - Commitment to Progress and Reform Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Committee for Informed Involvement, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Committee for Students' Concerns, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Committee in Solidarity with People of Iran, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Committee on Draft Education (CODE), 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Committee on Religious Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Committee to Elect Daryl Holter at UWM, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Committee to Fight the Cutbacks, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Common Cause, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Common Sense Party at UWM, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Communications and Mass Communications Association, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Community and Cultures Incorporated: Physics, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Concerned Students for International Rapprochement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Concerned Women for America, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Concert Choir, 1962-1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Concerts at UWM, 1982-1991 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - Conference on Inter-American Student Projects, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Congress of Student Social Workers, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - Congressional Information Network at UWM, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Conservation Club, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Consumer Affairs Student Organization, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Cornerstone League, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Council for Exceptional Children, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Council for World Freedom, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Council of Engineering Student Organizations, 1975-1992 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - Council on International Relations & United Nations Affairs, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Course and Faculty Evaluation Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Criminal Justice Student Association, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Crossroads
      - 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Lawsuit, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Cuban Forum, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Cultural Arts, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Cultural Arts Student Express, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - Cultural Organization of Persian Students, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - Culture Abroad, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Cycling Club, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Dalton Society, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Dames Club, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Dance Association, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - Dance Club, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Davison Cricket Appreciation Society, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Day Care Advocates, 1973-1986 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - Dead Circus Company, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - Deaf Student Association, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - Dean of Instruction, 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Dean of Men, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Dean of Student Affairs, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 48-52)
    - Debators at UWM, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Debate Team, 1957-1979 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Debate Team, Newsclippings and Flyers, 1962-1979 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Deeper Roots Fellowship, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 124)
    - Deliverance, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Delta Chi
      - 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Delta Chi Sigma
      - 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - 1957-1973 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Delta Fraternity, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 125)
    - Delta Kappa
      - 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - 1957-1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Delta Omicron, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Delta Phi Epsilon, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Delta Psi Chi Fraternity, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 126)
    - Delta Sigma Kappa
      - 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - 1957-1970 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Delta Sigma Rho, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Delta Tau Delta, 1959-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Delta Tau Kappa, 1964-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Delta Zeta, 1950-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Delta Zeta Epsilon Sorority at UWM, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    - Demonstrations, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Deutscher Verein, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Disciples, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Disco Club, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Ditrinetic Religious Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Divine Light Club, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dorado Club, 1957-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Dragon Club, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Du Bois Club, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Duane Gay for Assembly Student Committee, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Earth and Magical Religions on Campus, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - East Side Bible Study, 1979-1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Echo, 1944-1950 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Eckankar International Student Society, 1974-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Economic Club, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Economics Club, 1959-1967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Educational Psychology Graduate Association, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Educational Workers Industrial Union No. 620, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Eight Fifty Nine Club, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Elementary Division, 1946-1956 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - The Empire, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - EMIT, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Emperor Mathematics Improvement Students, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - EMS, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Engineers' Club, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - English Club, 1957-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Environs Film Society, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Epilepsy Association of Southeast Wisconsin at UWM, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Episcopal Campus Rectory, 1962-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Equestrian Club, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Escape, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Escape From Milwaukee Club, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Eta Kau Pi, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Eta Sigma Phi, 1957-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Ethiopian Famine and Refugee Relief Committee at UWM, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Ethiopian Students Union, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Every Now and Then Film Society, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Exceptional Division, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Experimental Drama, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Experimental Music Society, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Facet Magazine, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Far-Out-Flix, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Federation of University Assistants, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Fellowship of Benjamin Franklin, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Feminist Center of UWM, 1973-1984 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
    - Feminists for Life of Wisconsin, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Film Department Student Union, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Film Society at UWM, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Fine Arts and Cultural Enrichment, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Fine Arts Dance Club, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Fine Arts Music Club, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Fireside Theatre Group, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Fly By Night Film Society, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Folk Dance Group, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Folk Sing, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Folklore Society, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - The Force, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Forte: Film, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Fortnightly, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Forty-Second Street Film Society, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Forum: American Israeli Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Forum/Major Speakers Organization, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Forum on Conscientious Objection and the Draft, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Fourth of July Club, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Fraternities
      - 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Expansion, 1959-1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Policies, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Fraternities and Sororities, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Fraternity Scholarship Reports, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Free Speech, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Free Spirit Gang, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Free University, 1966-1977 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - French Club, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Friends Across the World, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Friends for a Cooperative Law School at UWM, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Friends for Brown, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Friends of Africa, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Friends of Eurythmy, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Friends of Free Schools, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Friends of Fun, Student Travel Club, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Friends of Kaleidoscope, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Friends of Pat Lucey & M. Schrieber, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Friends of Roots Cooperative, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Friends of Spartacus Youth League, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Friends of the Arboretum, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Friends of the Association for Humanist Psychology, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Friends of the Eighth Note Coffeehouse, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Friends of the Guardian, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Friends of the Indochinese People, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Friends of the Indo-Chinese People at UWM, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Friends of the Milwaukee Tenant Union, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Friends of the Rap House, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Friends of the UWM Union Art Gallery, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Friends of Women's Transit Service, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Fritz Blitz, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - "From the Dean's Den," 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Full Gospel Assembly, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Gamers Guild, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Gamma Delta
      - 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Gamma Delta Iota, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Gamma Phi Beta, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Gamma Sigma Sigma, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Gamma Theta Delta, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Gamma Theta Upsilon
      - 1957-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - 1957-1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Financial Records, 1949-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Minutes, 1950-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Programs, 1950-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Scrapbook, 1950-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Gay Christian Outreach, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Gay Peoples Union, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Gay Students Association, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Gelmetal Movement Company, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - General Semantics, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Geography Club, 1944-1959 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Geography Graduate Students Association, 1974-1984 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Geology Club, 1964, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Geophysical Society, 1975-1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - German Club, 1939-1963 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Gibbons Club, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Global Outreach, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Golf Club, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Good Government, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Good Kids at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Government in Gear, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Graduate Business Association, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Graduate Social Work Club, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Student Organization, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Graduate Students in Education, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Graduates in Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Greater Opportunities, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Greek Student Association, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Greek Week, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Green Party, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Group Against Smokers' Pollution, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Group Jay, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Groupo Estaudiantil Puertorriqueno, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Guide for Social Chairmen, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Guide for Student Organizations, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Guidon, 1966-1979 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Guild Student Group, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Gurdjieff -Nyland Milwaukee Group, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Gymnastics Club, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Half-Baked Theater Troupe, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hamagshimim, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Handball Club, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Handicapped Students League, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hang Gliding Club, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Harris for President-UWM, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Health Center Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hellas Greek Student Association, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hispanic Graduate Student Association, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Hispanic Intellectuals of Milwaukee, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Hispanic Student Alliance, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - History Club, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - History Graduate Assistants Club, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Holiday Singers, 1958-1966 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Holton Hall
      - 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - 1969 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Homecoming, 1958-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8-11)
    - Homosexual Freedom League, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Honor Societies of the College, 1953-1957, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Honoratae, Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Hot Air Ballooning Club, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - House Party, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Housing Rules, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Human Relations Council, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Human Rights Organization, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Humans Advocating Humor and Amusement, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Hunger Project at UWM, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Ibero-American Studies Society, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Imagen Latina, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Improving our Union (IOU), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Independent Coalition, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Independent Election Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Independent, Responsible Students (I.R.S.), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Independent Student Opportunities, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Independents for McCarthy, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - India Cultural Society, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Indian Community Day Care, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Indian Student Association, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Inner-City Community Resources, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Inter-Arts League 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Inter-Cultural Association, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Inter-Greek Council, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Inter-Normal Forensic League, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Inter-Sorority Council, 1947-1957 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Intercampus, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Intercollegiate Association of Women Students, 1960-1975 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Intercollegiate Knights, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Interdorm Council, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Interested Veterans of Central City, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Interfraternity Council, 1947-1981 (Box 4, Folder 29-31)
    - Interfraternity Council, Activities, 1966-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - International Association of Business Communications, 1988-1994 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - International Business Students Association, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - International Cultural Club, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - International Folk Dancers at UWM, 1975-1985 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - International Friendship Ministry, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - International Greek Expansion Council, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - International Muslim Student Organization, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - International Relations Club, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - International Students Club, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - International Television Association, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Investment Finance Group, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Iota Chi Sorority, 1968-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Iranian Students Organization, 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Islamic Information Service, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Israeli Student Organization, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Ivy Publications, 1957-1969 (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
    - Japanese Karate Club at UWM, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Jazz Ensemble, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Jazz Street, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Jesse Jackson for President '88, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Jesus People, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Jewish Student Movement, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Jewish Student Union, 1981-1994 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Jim Wood for Governor, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - John Brown Revolutionary Brigade, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - John Tudor Fan Club, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Johnston Hall, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Johnston Hall, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Joseph Conrad Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Jude III, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Judo Club, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Judo-Kodokan Judo Klub, 1969-1991 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Judo Team at UWM, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Juggling Society at UWM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Junior American Pharmaceutical Association, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Junior Class, 1953-1957 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Justice & Peace Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Kappa Delta Pu, 1958-1982 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Kappa Lambda Iota, 1950-1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kappa Upsilon Nu Tau, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Karate Club, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Kennedy for President, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Kenwood Hall, 1949-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kindergarten Primary Association, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Krishna Yoga Society, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Krishnamurti Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - L5 at UWM, 1978-1982 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - La Colectiva, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - La Onda Latina, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Labor Farm Party, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Lambda Chi Alpha, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Lambda Phi Chi, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Laotian-American Student Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Latin Club, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Latinos Unidos, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Latter Day Saints Student Association, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Lavender Commitment, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - League of United Latin American Citizens, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Letterman's Club, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Liaison Social Service Organization, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Liberal Club, 1961-1965, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Liberal Programmers, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Life Sciences Organization, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Lifesaving Corps, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Literary Club at UWM, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Living Art Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Los Universitarios, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Lutheran Collegians, 1965-1986 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Lutheran Student Association of Metropolitan Milwaukee, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Lutheran Student Fellowship, 1968-1993 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Lutheran Students Association, 1938-1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - M & G Social Club, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Macintosh Users Group at UWM, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Magic Lantern Film Society, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Majority Coalition, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Make Opportunity Available Now, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Malaysian Business and Liberal Arts Association, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Malaysian Student Association, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Margaret-Mary Ann Pageant Dancers, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Marietta House, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Mario Cuomo for President, 1988, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Market Reach, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Marketiers of UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Marketing Club, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Martial Arts Club, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Marxists in Academia, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Masada, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Masters Swim Club, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Math Club, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Mathematics Club, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - McCarthy for President Club, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - McLaren Hall, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - McLaren Hall Association, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Medical Club, 1919-1922 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Medical Technologists Club, 1965-1981 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Medieval Gaming Association, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Meditation Society at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Meeting of the Mimes, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Meher Baba Information, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Member of Science Society, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Men's Chorus, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Men's Glee Club, 1930, 1958-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Men's Physical Education Club, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Men's Press Club, 1964, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)